Let's go home, Riko-chan.
Yeah!
Riko-chan?
Okay, job's done.
You're free to go now.
Why are you here?
Why?
Oh, that's what you mean.
Because I killed Satoru Gojo.
Is that so?
Die!
Don't be so impatient.
Episode 27
Hidden Inventory 4
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Hidden Inventory/Premature Death
The Tombs of the Star
and the Forbidden Vault
use barriers that conceal.
So they can't place guards at the entrances.
As long as you know where the doors are,
they're full of holes.
Sorcerers are busy during this time of year,
and Jujutsu High is brimming
with Fly Heads right now.
It's pure chaos outside.
And since I have no cursed energy,
I'm like the invisible man.
There was one problem, though.
If I wield a cursed tool,
the cursed energy from it will stop
me from being an invisible man.
Now, there's more to this story.
See, I keep a cursed spirit
capable of storing objects around.
So I usually put my cursed tools
in it when I'm walking around.
You don't have to say it.
Yes, that means the cursed energy from
the cursed spirit should stop me
from being an invisible man.
So I make the cursed spirit smaller,
until it can fit inside my body.
Then I keep it inside my stomach.
After all, the organs of the invisible
man are invisible, too, right?
That's how I'm able to
pass through any barrier
while still carrying
all kinds of cursed tools.
That's also why I didn't use
a cursed tool at first.
A surprise attack on the Six Eyes
would be pointless if I wasn't invisible.
I could've killed the Star Plasma Vessel first,
but the risk of the Six Eyes seeing me was too—
Enough.
You have a Heavenly Pact, right?
I know revealing information about
your ability increases its fundamental
strength, just like for a sorcerer.
That's not what I want to know.
How did you know which doors
led to the Tombs of the Star?
We didn't leave even
the slightest residuals.
Humans leave plenty of
traces aside from residuals.
Like scents, footprints, and so on.
My pact enhances all five of my senses, too.
There should have been
another woman on the way here.
What happened to her?
Hm?
Oh, that maid?
She's probably dead.
I didn't care if she lived or died, though.
If she's lucky, she might still be alive.
Is that so?
You really should... die!
That Rainbow Dragon has
the toughest hide there is!
Curse Manipulation...
Riffraff.
Hey, am...
Am... Am I...
pretty?
A potential apparition?
It deploys a simple domain that
enforces non-violence on both of us
until I answer its question, then?
Ah, well...
Then I'll just come out and say
you're not my type.
So that's how it is.
Idiot.
It's over.
For you!
Curse Manipulation.
It's a technique that lets me
absorb cursed spirits
that have surrendered,
and freely manipulate them.
If there's roughly a two-grade
difference in our levels,
I skip making them submit
and absorb them unconditionally.
His cursed spirit may have a unique ability,
but it's not that strong itself.
I can absorb it. That'll lock down his armory.
Then I can just brute-force him—
I didn't cut you badly enough to kill you.
I would've killed you if
you were a shikigami user,
but since it's Curse Manipulation,
there's no telling what might happen to the
cursed spirits you've absorbed after you die.
I'd rather avoid extra trouble here.
You have the blessing of parentage.
But even with that blessing,
you were all beaten by a monkey like me
who can't even use cursed techniques.
If you want to live a long life,
never forget that.
Oh, speaking of blessings...
That's right. I almost forgot.
I named him Megumi.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Star Religious Group Headquarters
House of the Children of the Star
Go on, now.
The corpse of the Star Plasma
Vessel, Riko Amanai.
All four limbs intact, too.
Hmm, indeed.
We'll issue your payment as we discussed.
m 0 0 l 136 0 l 136 200 l 0 200
Star
Religious Group
Representative
Shigeru
Sonoda
I'll even throw in a bonus.
Thank you, Founder.
You're so generous.
He's not the founder.
Huh?
Do you mean it?
I know it was a necessary expense,
but you've already helped us out a lot, too.
I thought you'd complain a bit more.
We hired you for the assassination
expecting that it would fail.
Our Star Religious Group
was founded in the Nara Era,
when Tengen-sama began preaching
about the moral foundation
of jujutsu sorcerers,
a minority, as Buddhism
spread throughout Japan.
Jujutsu society and religious corporations
are at complete odds with each other.
That strain is what gave birth
to our modern Star Religious Group,
the Time Vessel Association.
That is also why we have devoted
ourselves to remaining non-sorcerers.
Jujutsu sorcerers are granted
many privileges above the law,
but they're still fundamentally forbidden
to lay a hand on non-sorcerers.
However, the time had finally arrived.
The time of the taboo
recorded in our scriptures!
Our Star Religious Group has evolved to
a monotheistic religion
worshiping one absolute god!
And it was now time for our object of
worship to assimilate with that impurity!
If our believers saw us simply sit back
and watch the assimilation happen,
our Association would crumble.
Yet if we took excessive action,
jujutsu sorcerers would crush us.
So we were truly desperate.
And how did it all turn out?
We thought we were going to lose everything,
and now we have it all!
Of course that would
loosen our purse strings.
Human society might be what crumbles
if Tengen-sama loses control, though.
If we should perish along with our star,
then that is all there is to it.
Were you referring to Okinawa
when you said they helped us?
Yeah.
Why didn't you kill the maid then?
I know I told you,
"Take her someplace far away,
and kill her at some point."
Because I had a good idea of what
you were planning at the time.
I made the call that the relief
from the maid's successful rescue
would wear him down more than
heightened tensions from failure.
You often ignore the lines of communication
and toss out whatever I was planning, right?
It all worked out in the end.
And stop running your mediator ragged.
Yeah, but why Okinawa?
I had a laugh at that myself.
Normally, you'd use a car
to transport a captive, right?
Public transportation carries
too many risks, after all.
But get this. The president
owned his own private jet.
Even so...
Rich people think on a different scale, man.
Well, let's go eat with their money.
Take me to one of the
restaurants you use for clients.
No way.
You never pay for a guy, anyway.
I've already decided I'll only see you
either for work or in Hell.
Huh?
Hey, it's been a while.
For real?
For real, real.
I'm alive and kicking!
Reverse cursed technique!
Bingo!
When you stabbed me through the throat,
I gave up on counterattacking
and poured all my focus into
the reverse cursed technique.
Cursed energy is negative energy.
While it can enhance the body,
it can't regenerate it.
So you multiply that negative energy
against itself to create positive energy.
That's the reverse cursed technique.
Easier said than done!
I hadn't been able to do
that up until now myself!
And I couldn't understand anything
the one person who could do it said!
He's blabbing on and on...
He's high.
But I finally grasped it
on the verge of death!
The true essence of cursed energy!
The reason you're going to lose is
because you didn't chop my head off,
and because you didn't use that cursed
tool when you stabbed my head.
I'm going to lose?
Our fight is just getting started.
Oh? Is it?
Yeah...
Maybe so!
Cursed Technique Reversal:
Red.
Monster.
No bones are broken.
That shock wave was an
application of Limitless,
the cursed technique reversal, Red, huh?
So he poured the positive energy generated
by the reverse cursed technique
into the Limitless
technique ingrained into him.
One, the power to stop:
the neutral application
of the Limitless technique.
Two, the power to attract:
the amplified application of
the Limitless technique, Blue.
And three, the power to repel:
the reversal of his cursed technique, Red.
All things I can handle.
Something's off.
No, this is fine.
I'll kill you.
Sorry, Amanai.
I'm not even angry over you right now.
I bear no grudge against anyone.
It's just that the world feels
so, so wonderful right now.
"Throughout Heaven and Earth,
I alone am the honored one."
The merit of having a technique
that's passed down for generations
is having a user's manual.
The demerit is that
information about the
technique is easily leaked.
You were a member of
the Zen'in clan, weren't you?
That's why you know so much
about the Limitless technique.
However, even in the Gojo clan,
only a scant few know about this.
Take the amplified and the reversal,
then smash together those
two different expressions
of infinity to create and
push out imaginary mass.
Imaginary Technique: Purple.
Something's off.
"I refuse to do any work for free."
Normally I would've said that
and hightailed it out of there.
Yet the freshly awakened wielder of the
Limitless technique was right before my eyes.
He was probably the strongest jujutsu
sorcerer of the modern age.
I wanted to reject him.
I wanted to bring him to his knees.
I wanted to take down the
pinnacle of the jujutsu world
and the Zen'in clan that rejected me.
I twisted myself to try to affirm myself.
That was the moment I lost.
I thought you had abandoned that pride.
I thought you had chosen to live without
respecting yourself or anyone else.
Any last words?
Nah.
Two or three years from now,
my kid will be sold off to the Zen'in clan.
Do what you will with that.
Mommy!
Hug me!
You're late, Suguru.
No, I guess you got here fast.
There are several Star Religious
Group facilities in the city, after all.
Satoru? Is that you?
What happened?
I see you already saw Shoko.
Yeah, she healed me.
I'm fine now.
No, me being safe doesn't
help anything here.
I screwed up.
You're not at fault.
Let's head back.
Suguru, should we kill these guys?
The way I feel right now,
I doubt I'd feel anything about it.
No. There's no point.
It looks like there are only
common believers here.
The masterminds who know about our
world have probably fled already.
And unlike with the bounty,
they won't be able to
talk their way out of this.
The organization had
problems to begin with.
It'll be dissolved soon enough.
No point, huh?
Does there really need
to be any point to it?
It's very important that there is.
Especially for a jujutsu sorcerer.
I wonder if whoever came up with the phrase
"a surprising side"
thought of people as cubes,
and if whoever came up with the insult
"shallow" thought of people as flat surfaces?
Next time, "Premature Death."
Next Episode
Premature Death
Either way, people do have two sides to them.